<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ben-dale.co.uk</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ben-dale.co.uk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
          <title>TryHackMe: Agent Sudo</title>
          <link>/posts/tryhackme-agent-sudo/</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/posts/tryhackme-agent-sudo/</guid>
          <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my write-up for Agent Sudo, a CTF challenge created by DesKel.
Write-up I deployed the box using TryHackMe&amp;rsquo;s interface and scanned the host using nmap:
kali@kali:~$ nmap -sC -sV 10.10.108.158 Starting Nmap 7.80 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2020-07-02 15:15 EDT Nmap scan report for 10.10.108.158 Host is up (0.021s latency). Not shown: 997 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 21/tcp open ftp vsftpd 3.0.3 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.6p1 Ubuntu 4ubuntu0.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>VulnHub: Cloud AV</title>
          <link>/posts/vulnhub-boredhackerblog-cloudav/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/posts/vulnhub-boredhackerblog-cloudav/</guid>
          <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my write-up for Cloud AV, a VulnHub box created by BorderHackerBlog.
Write-up The description for this box states the following:
Cloud Anti-Virus Scanner! is a cloud-based antivirus scanning service. Currently, it&amp;#39;s in beta mode. You&amp;#39;ve been asked to test the setup and find vulnerabilities and escalate privs. Difficulty: Easy Tasks involved: port scanning webapp attacks sql injection command injection brute forcing code analysis Virtual Machine: Format: Virtual Machine (Virtualbox OVA) Operating System: Linux Networking: DHCP Service: Enabled IP Address Automatically assign This works better with VirtualBox than VMware The listed tasks are exploits I have some familiarity with so I decided that this would be a good box to brush up some techniques.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>I forget when I&#39;m on the VPN</title>
          <link>/posts/on-vpn/</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/posts/on-vpn/</guid>
          <description>The COVID-19 breakout has resulted in me working from home for the foreseeable, which means I&amp;rsquo;m using the work VPN more than I&amp;rsquo;m used to. Typically I don&amp;rsquo;t have to use the work VPN as I tend to work in the office most of the time but being at home has me flipping in and out of the VPN a couple of times a day. One thing I keep forgetting about the VPN is whether I&amp;rsquo;m on it or not.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>VulnHub: Mr-Robot</title>
          <link>/posts/vulnhub-mr-robot/</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/posts/vulnhub-mr-robot/</guid>
          <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my write-up for Mr-Robot, a VulnHub box created by Leon Johnson.
Write-up The description for this box states the following:
Based on the show, Mr Robot. This VM has three keys hidden in different locations. Your goal is to find all three. Each key is progressively difficult to find. The VM isn&amp;#39;t too difficult. There isn&amp;#39;t any advanced exploitation or reverse engineering. The level is considered beginner-intermediate. Once I found out what IP the box was running on I scanned the ports using nmap:</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>VulnHub: HappyCorp</title>
          <link>/posts/vulnhub-happycorp/</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/posts/vulnhub-happycorp/</guid>
          <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my write-up for HappyCorp, a VulnHub box created by Zayotic.
Write-up The description for this box states the following:
+- - - - - - - - - - - - - -|- - - - - - - - - - - - - - -+ | Name: Happycorp | IP: DHCP | | Date: 2019-March-05 | Goal: Get Root! | | Author: Zayotic | Difficultly: ??? | +- - - - - - - - - - - - - -|- - - - - - - - - - - - - - -+ | | | + Average beginner/intermediate VM, only a few twists | | + May find it easy/hard (depends on YOUR background) | | + .</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>VulnHub: Sunset Nightfall</title>
          <link>/posts/vulnhub-sunset-nightfall/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/posts/vulnhub-sunset-nightfall/</guid>
          <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my write-up for Nightfall, a VulnHub box created by whitecr0wz, which is part of the Sunset series.
Write-up The description for this box states the following:
Nightfall is a born2root VM designed for beginners. Virtualbox is strongly recommended for doing this challenge. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t much to go off there so I ran a port scan using nmap to see what was running:
kali@kali:~/Documents/vulnhub/nightfall/nmap$ nmap -sV -sC -oA nmap 10.0.2.19 Starting Nmap 7.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>VulnHub: SP Eric</title>
          <link>/posts/my-first-writeup/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/posts/my-first-writeup/</guid>
          <description>This weekend I managed to fully root a VulnHub box without looking at another person&amp;rsquo;s write-up for a hint, for the first time! This box was created by Daniel Solstad and can be downloaded here. Here&amp;rsquo;s my write-up.
Write-up The description for this box states:
Eric is trying to reach out on the Internet, but is he following best practice? Flags: - /root/flag.txt - /home/eric/flag.txt Once I had Eric set up and running I ran a port scan:</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Text Clock</title>
          <link>/posts/text-clock/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/posts/text-clock/</guid>
          <description>A few years ago I came across a clock design that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen before. I thought the design was pretty cool and I wondered how hard it would be to build a webpage that would display similar wording that highlights to display the current time.
I got to work hacking around, figuring out how to translate time in numbers to time in text. After a couple of hours I had something I was fairly happy with.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>About</title>
          <link>/about/</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/about/</guid>
          <description>Software engineer based in Manchester, UK.</description>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>
